watashitachi (tensai)
We've decided (Genius!)
sukina koto dake shite (saikou)
That we're going to live this way (It's the best!)
ikiteku to kimetano (seikai)
Doing only the things that we like (That's right!)
anata mo rettou let's try drop out
Join us down here, let's try to drop out!
hai ten ni mashimasu warera no
hai aku no michi koso warera no
Yes, those of us who reside in Heaven
Yes, those of us that live on the path to evil
hai chichi naru kami ni kansha wo
hai sonzaiigi no hazu desho
Yes, we show gratitude to our Holy Father
Yes, this is surely why we exist here
hai kyou mo tadashiku ikitemasu
hai kyou mo meiwaku kaketemasu
Yes, we'll live proper, just lives today
Yes, to cause havoc in the lives of others today
hai yoku ni oborete ikitemasu
hai zenryoku de warubutte masu
Yes, we're going to drown in our own avarice!
Yes, we do our best to pretend to be evil!
kashiko
From yours truly!
netoge jaaji de gorogoro (everyday)
In my sweats, laying around playing online games (Everyday!)
souji sentaku akumagyou (majime)
Cleaning and laundry, it's a demon's job (So serious!)
yami ni ousama ni naru no (murigei)
I will become the Queen of Darkness (Unwinnable game!)
are ma minnasama okinodoku
Oh dear everyone, how pitiful
ochibureta toka iwasenai (dayone)
I won't let you say my life is completely ruined (That's right!)
dameninatta dake desune (demone)
You're just a little off track (But you know...)
atarashii kono sekai ni minna ni deaeta
And in this brand new world, I was able to meet all of you
tenshi no na no moto ni
In the name of all angels
akuma no na no moto ni
In the name of all demons
shukufuku wo (yes)
Blessings unto all (Yes!)
wazawai wo (yes)
Disaster unto all (Yes!)
hallelujah essaim
Hallelujah Essaim!
watashitachi (sensei)
All of us here now (We pledge!)
kono sekai ni orete (happy)
We descend upon this world (Happy!)
sunao ni naretakara (iijan)
We're being completely honest here (So it's okay!)
kono mama zutto zutto isshoni imasho
So let's all stay like this forever and ever
watashitachi (tensai)
We've decided (Genius!)
sukina koto dake shite (saikou)
That we're going to live this way (It's the best!)
ikiteku to kimetano (seikai)
Doing only the things that we like (That's right!)
anata mo rettou let's go
Join us down here, let's go!
arugamama e to rettou let's try drop out
Just like that, let's try to drop out!
hai ten ni mashimasu warera no
hai aku no michi koso warera no
Yes, those of us who reside in Heaven
Yes, those of us that live on the path to evil
hai chichi naru kami ni kansha wo
hai sonzaiigi no hazu desho
Yes, we show gratitude to our Holy Father
Yes, this is surely why we exist here
hai kyou mo tadashiku ikitemasu
hai kyou mo meiwaku kaketemasu
Yes, we'll live proper, just lives today
Yes, to cause havoc in the lives of others today
hai yoku ni oborete ikitemasu
hai zenryoku de warubutte masu
Yes, we're going to drown in our own avarice!
Yes, we do our best to pretend to be evil!
kashiko
From yours truly!