tenshi no hane hirogete
I'll spread wide my angel's wings
minna ni shukufuku wo
And deliver joy and peace to the world
Man, singing's effort.
Will you snap out of it already?!
You're an angel!
Muahahaha!
Isn't the weather heavenly
today? Good day, everyone.
Can't someone do it for
me for, like, 10 yen?
I am the ultimate archdemon!
My name shakes the heavens!
You look so exhilarated, studying
and working like worker ants.
So start acting angelic
and do your job!
I microtransactioned
too hard, so I'm broke.
They gave me a ton of gems
for that stupid server error,
Be grateful that you can
breathe the same CO2 as me!
Look, I'm a demon, so I'm acting
demonic and doing my job.
Would you care for
some sugar water?
What? You wouldn't?
so I'm good for now, but
next month's gonna suck.
Wait, am I?
What? What do you mean,
I'm wrong? We breathe oxygen?
I'm so sorry, you were a
worker bee, not a worker ant!
What does it mean to
act demonic, anyway?
Dammit. Can't some money
just fall from Heaven?
U-Um, well, we call
it that in Hell!
netoge dake shitetai wa
All I wanna do is grind my MMOs
chotto heya kurai katadzukete
At least try to clean up your room!
kyou mo omocha wa genki da wa
My favorite toy is as lively as ever today
inu kowa yamete utaenai ja nai
A dog?! No! Stop it! I can't sing like this!
aa jinrui horobinai kana
Man, can't humanity just go to Hell?
tenshirashiku chanto yatte yo
At least try to act like an angel!
daiakumasama no odemashi desu
Hark! The Archdemon has arrived!
ware koso wa daiakuma
I am the Archdemon
Hey! You listening?!
tte kiiten no
guutara guutara tengoku da wa kore
I can choose to snooze, this is what I call heaven
hito ni yasashiku jibun ni kibishiku
Soft on others, hard on herself
akuma no you na tenshi no egao
The smile of an angel almost like a demon
watashi wo dare dato omotteiru no yo
Who the heck do you think I am?!
jouge kaiten
Rolling now to cross the floor
tenma hanten
As an angel, you're done for
keisei gyakuten
Look out for the trap door
kibou wa anten
One thing I'm living for
pride douten
Pride? I had that once before
amame no saiten
Easy judgment on the score
egao de manten
A smile worth an encore
pashitte baiten
Running to the store
torima JK da shi
Like, I'm a high school girl
seifuku kitara ii kanji
Put on my uniform and my job's done
people mo demon mo angel mo hikkurumete hai (happy)
People and demons and angels
Jumble them all up, and there (Happy!)
nandemo iin ja nai (fuu fuu)
Whatever happens is fine (Woohoo!)
heaven mo hell mo earth mo gochamaze de hai (happy)
Heaven and Hell and Earth
Mix them all up, and there (Happy!)
minna de gakkou ikou (fuu)
Let's all go to school (Woo!)
sukkoronde wa (wa)
Trip up and fall (Yeah!)
donaubette wa (wa)
Roll into the wall (Yeah!)
uei (uei) uei (uei)
Yay! (Yay!) Yay! (Yay!)
datte tenshi desu mono
I'm an angel, you know