(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
succhau zo
I'll suck you
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
yappari
absolutely
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
yakousei
nocturnally
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
ichiban desu
the best one
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
kimi mo
why don't we
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
issho ni odotte mimasen ka
go and dance together
Yes!
chotto okashii na meguri ai demo
Although this is a rather strange encounter
taisetsu ni shimasen ka
Will you treasure it?
makkurana sora ni wa otsukisama
O Moon in the dark sky
sutekina 「hajimemashite」
What a lovely "Nice to meet you!"
kitto hontou no kimochi wa kagami ni wa utsuranai
This honest feeling is definitely not reflected in the mirror
chotto baka hen datte sore mo go aikyou desu
Even if it's a bit weird, it's also charming
fushigi o ai shimashou
Let's love the weirdness
We are the †Kyutie Ladies† nante wonderful!
We are the †Kyutie Ladies†, how wonderful!
hoshizora no shita wa Dance Hall
Under the starry sky is a Dance Hall
†Kyutie Ladies† pajama no mama
†Kyutie Ladies† with this pajama
asa ga kuru made wa jiyuu jikan
We could do anything 'til morning comes
nee, watashitachi tomodachi deshou
Hey, we are friends, right?
We are the †Kyutie†
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
succhau zo
I'll suck you
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
yappari
absolutely
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
yakousei
nocturnally
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
ichiban desu
the best one
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
kimi mo
why don't we
(Chu! Chu! Chu!)
issho ni odotte mimasen ka
go and dance together
Yes!