sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
Yes, curry is my favorite
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
But if I may be a bit greedy
amakuchi ga iindeshou
You prefer it mild, don't you?
mou nebaneba datte mo mochiron
Oh, but sticky food is fine by me too
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
I can eat it, no problem
nigate nan dana
You don't like it, do you?
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
kore demo shikkari kojuuto datte shimasu
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
senobi shicchatte (yes!)
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
sore ni anzangata desushi
And you've got great child-bearing hips
ki ni shiteru noni
Hey, I'm conscious of that
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
You're so crazy at home
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
Did you brainwash the people at school?
shitto shichatte mou (more!)
Aww, don't be jealous (More!)
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
chakkari to ima sennyuu seikou
And now we've finally snuck into your heart
Once we get close to each other
nakayoku nattara
uchiakenakya demo
And we have to be frank
aimai na koto
Will we still be able to understand
rikai dekiru kana
What's left unsaid?
My love for snacks and other things
sorya maa oyatsu toka
May make me seem childish
kodomoppoi desu ga
sore demo zutto nakayokushite kuremasuka
But will you still be my friend forever?