kore wa kamisama no itazura kamo
This might be God's mischief
deai wa totsuzen ne
or a sudden encounter
watashitachi chotto fuugawari jikaku wa nashi
We are kinda strange, with no self-awareness
demo wakari aeru heart
But our hearts can understand each other
tamani cooking shimashou
Let's cook once in a while
sore kara ne onaji bed de naisho banashi shiyou
Then, sharing secrets on the same bed
HAPPY!! strange friends
Happy!! Strange Friends!
watashitachi zutto issho ne yakusoku
Let's promise we'll always be together
shiawase rhythm
with a happy rhythm
kimi dake sukoshi tempo ga zurete mo
Even if you missed a little tempo
egao de dokidoki shinagara
I throbbed with a smile
ichiban ni iitai no「ohayo」tte
while really wanting to say “Good morning!”
HAPPY!! strange friends
Happy!! Strange Friends!
tempo ga zurete mo heiki yo
Even if you missed the tempo, it's fine
egao de dokidoki sowasowa shinagara
I nervously throbbed with a smile
ichiban ni iitai no「ohayo」tte
while really wanting to say “Good morning!”
itsumademo
Forever and ever