Original Work
Amatou “Tonari no Kyuuketsuki-san”
(Monthly Comic Cune Serialization / Kadokawa Publication)
Planning
Masahide Tsuji
Takeshi Kikuchi
Yoshikuni Murata
Masayuki Aoyagi
Asuka Yamazaki
Makoto Hojo
Katsuya Nagahata
Tomonori Shibata
Tomonari Sakai
Series Composition
Tatsuya Takahashi
Character Design
Takahiro Sakai
Chief Animation Director
Concept Design
Prop Design
Sonomi Sugimura
Shigeyuki Koresawa (Digital Noise)
Tom (Digital Noise)
Art Director
Color Deisign
Director of Photography
Editing
Hiroki Matsumoto (Atelier Platz)
Yoko Suzuki
Takeshi Hirooka
Kentarou Tsubone
Sound Director
Music
Music Producer
Music Production
Jin Aketagawa
Fujisawa Yoshiaki
Shin Ikaga
Nippon Columbia
Opening Theme
“†Kyutie Ladies†”
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement : Kentaro Sonoda
Performed by :
Sophie Twilight (CV: Miyu Tomita)
Akari Amano (CV: Yū Sasahara)
Hinata Natsuki (CV: Lynn)
Elly (CV: Azumi Waki)
Producer
Takayuki Matsunaga
Sachi Kawamoto
Fumiki Yamazaki
Shouma Yamamoto
Noritomo Isogai
Tomohiro Kashiwaya
Yuichi Izumi
Marina Tanaka
Animation Producer
Tetsuya Tomioka
Animation Production
Animation
Studio
アクシズ
Assistant Director
Toshinori Fukushima
Director
Noriaki Akitaya
Production
Tonari no Kyuuketsuki-san Production Committee